Gelvin De Leon

Web Developer/Graphic Designer

8 years of Web Development and Graphic Design experience.

As a web developer, a firm believer in responsive design, mobile-first approach, and driven on using technology to solve problems. Passionate for creating not only enticing designs, but also effective designs that provide a solution.

Calgary, AB +13682993634 deleon.gelvin@gmail.com

Skills

- Hard Skills: HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, JQuery, Git, ASP.NET, ReactJS, WordPress, Php, Figma, Responsive Web Design, Object Oriented Programming, MySQL, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Premiere, Microsoft Word, Excel, Powerpoint
- **Soft Skills:** Creative, analytical thinking, continuous learning, attention to detail, resolving technical issues, dedication, commitment, responsibility, teamwork, adaptability

Work Experience

Front-end Web Developer (Remote)

Platform 3 Inc. Key Media

November 2020 - September 2023

- Managed web content updates, provided consultation on newsletter coordinators for web and email related concerns, and created graphic design and mockups.
- Developed websites as a Front end Web Developer using Wordpress. This also includes converting figma
 wireframes to bootstrap based html file, Ensuring optimization and cross browser and device compatibility,
 assisting stakeholders, editorial and events team for content changes, and acting as point person for CMS related
 concerns.
- Built reusable codes for future use, ensured the technical feasibility of UI/UX design.
- Created and designed email templates for EDM send outs.
- Created, edited, and optimized image assets for web use.

Freelance Graphics Designer

Wert Philippines

January 2020 - October 2020

- Provided Detailing Aid, Catchcovers and Leaflet graphic designs for Wert Philippines' healthcare and wellness products: Calcidat OB, Calciday Ortho, and Perispa.
- Created a logo, packaging, and pillow pouch design with 4 different variants for Yummy Vites.
- Provided Box and Bottle label design for REZYD Throat Spray.

Front-end Web Developer

C88 Financial Technologies Pte Ltd

July 2014 - November 2019

- Developed websites as a Front end Web Developer In asp.net. This also includes making each website responsive for different screen resolutions and different mobile devices.
- Handled and created Microsoft Sharepoint pages and Microsoft Stream for internal company use.
- Provided graphic designs, page designs, email templates, and instructional videos.

Freelance Front-end Web Developer/Designer

Dalaroy Beach Resort March 2018

• Created the web design and developed the website for Dalaroy Beach Resort. The website is developed using HTML, CSS, SCSS. Javascript, Bootstrap, Jquery, and Google Maps.

Front-end Web Developer

Cube International January 2014 - June 2014

• Developed websites for different clients as a Front end Web Developer. This also includes making each website responsive for different screen resolutions and different mobile devices.

Education

De La Salle University, Manila

June 2009 - June 2014

Bachelor of Science degree in Computer Studies with specialization in Instructional Systems Technology Dean's List: 3rd Term, AY 2010-2011; 1st Term, AY 2011-2012; 2nd Term, AY 2011-2012.



Verified International Academic Qualifications - Issued by World Education Services

Equivalency in Canada: Bachelor's degree (four years)

Portfolio

https://del22vin.github.io/

Certificates

•	Get started using Google Analytics	2023
	Skillshop - Cert No: 57183 212665248	
	https://skillshop.credential.net/77f9e7b9-575c-4f8d-8e0f-9377496dbc7a	
•	Graphic Design	2023
	Alison - Cert No:1926-34108935	
	https://alison.com/certification/check/2y10jOTfpegKiSEvHhSMcHc2meagS7ZRhd4naHhBMQYAK1O2GwVC7Oq	
•	Wordpress CMS	2023
	Inventive Media	
•	Google Analytics for Beginners	2022
	Google Analytics Academy	
•	What is Graphic Design?	2022
	LinkedIn Learning - Certificate Id: AZg7HawSnchgKYrndtRczz9qkIFk	
•	Graphic Design Careers: First Steps	2022
	LinkedIn Learning - Certificate Id: ASnOeXrlbmLGzyi1p8L2hEMT_K_k	
•	HTML & CSS with Bootstrap	2022
	Inventive Media	
•	Mastering React	2020
	Mosh Coding Made Simple - Cert No: cert_drhmpg32	
•	Adobe Premiere Pro CC Training Course	2019
	Inventive Media	